欢迎观看冬季裙装制作教程。欢迎观看冬季裙装制作教程。
欢迎观看冬季裙装制作教程。
首先请从Library窗口中加载虚拟模特。
接着切换到Modular Configurator,打开Women,T-shirt,Setting。
选择模块Body,Setting Run,Sleeves,Setting Run。
安排好袖子版片。
接下来我们要将它调整成公主线款式,在修改之前移除模块化关系。
沿着厚中创建一条内部线。
剪切缝纫这条内部线。
在厚中腰部位置增加点以制作嗓道。
将点向内移动收缩腰围。
使用线段3D版片工具绘制公主线。
点击起始点随后在胸部腰部点击增加短线。
便于后续调整。
将3D线段转换为内部图形。
调整这些断点让线段过度更自然。
将腰部点向内移动减少腰围。
选择公主线剪切缝纫。
移动腰部断点继续将腰围缩小。
删除板片侧边线段上的曲线点便于后续调整侧边线段。
把后腰窝的点向内移动让后中线段贴合人体图形。
把后腰窝的点向内移动让后中线段贴合人体曲线从而抹平后腰的这个褶子。
现在虚拟模特腰部有一些褶子堆积是因为腰线太靠上了。
选中所有腰部点按方向键下从而将腰部最细位置向下调整以匹配模特的真正腰线。
Select all the waist points and press the direction button to adjust the waist to the lowest position in order to match the model's real waist line
Then the sleeves and the top are sewed together
Now the bottom of the princess line is too out of place to select the bottom two points to move to the front
Then move the chest point to increase the chest circumference of the outfit to reduce the side wrinkles caused by the chest being too tight
Then do the skirt part
Use the editor tool to select all the lower lines
Press ctrl a and then press ctrl h to print all the panels
Printed panels can reduce the wrinkles on the panels to make the simulation more stable and then adjust the bottom point to widen the skirt
Change the particle diameter to 20 mm
Continue to adjust the back skirt to make a decoupling
Press ctrl a and then press ctrl h to adjust the back skirt to make a decoupling
Open the simulation drag the panel so that the panel is exactly on the bottom
Then continue to drag the bottom of the front panel to increase the skirt length
Look at the length of the side line of the front panel
Right-click on the back side line and select the length to be adjusted to equal to the length of the side line of the front panel
Press c to switch to the editor tool
Adjust the curve of the skirt
Then continue to widen the front skirt and adjust the curve
Open the simulation due to the hardening of the panel drag the panel to quickly return to the correct simulation effect
You can adjust the outfit in the 3D window to simulate the right effect and you can also use the 3D effect to repeatedly adjust the panel in the 2D window
Press ctrl a and then ctrl h
To remove the hardening of all panels
Freeze all panels and unfreeze the sleeve panels
Next, adjust the sleeves to a medium-sized style of large sleeves
Maintain the hardening of the sleeve panels to make it easier to adjust later
Add a straight line near the elbow position
Use the function of changing the length to widen the seam
Please note that the function of changing the length is directional
Here we have to choose both
That is, to modify it to both ends
Then use the editor warning tool and verz tools
to drag the side of the sleeve and the sleeve entrance to modify the curves
B2
wrong
It's important to dead
O
Set the pressure value to simulate the insertion part more quickly, and then change the pressure value to 0.
Use the
tool to modify the transition part of the elbow part.
Click on the pivot point, then drag the mouse to preview the adjustment effect.
In the process of dragging, press the mouse button to open and enter the window of the specific value.
Set the same value for the transition curve on both sides of the left and right to ensure that there is no problem with the sewing line.
Then you can continue to adjust the side curve of the sleeves to ensure that they are symmetrical.
Next, let's create the sleeve version.
Select the sleeve line section, use the internal line
to create a line to cut out the inner line of the sleeve version, then cut the seam.
We are going to start making the anti-activation sleeve version.
Before we closed the library window, click on the reset interface layout in the lower right corner to reopen it.
Add the mailhoodie file to the work area.
Click on the
delete file to delete all the files except the hat version.
Extend the neck down a little bit, then adjust the curve.
Then adjust the bottom plate of the sleeve.
Because we just extended the collar,
we also need to make the curve of the sleeve bottom plate.
The curve of the sleeve is also a little bit deeper.
Use the free sewing tool to sew the back collar and the hat.
Here we create an equal length of the sleeve line according to the blue index point.
Then sew the front collar and the hat to the same length of the line.
Use the BNC sewing line tool to select the right button after the sewing line.
Select the end point of the sewing line, add a point.
Delete all the curve points, let the extra line become a straight line.
Then sew the left and right sides together.
In order to prevent the hat from slipping,
we can press W, click on the top of the hat,
add a fixed pin, and fix the hat.
Adjust the shape of the hat.
When we lengthen the sleeve, the right side will also be longer on both sides.
When we adjust the back and center curve, the depth of the hat will also be increased.
You can also put the entire sleeve together.
The hardening of the sleeve allows the hat to quickly organize the appropriate shape.
First, we can refer to the effect of the 3D window while adjusting the line at the cross section.
Move the front and middle bottom points upwards to shorten the length of the outline of the hat.
Lengthening the bottom line of the hat makes the hat deeper,
and the fold will be deeper at the collar of the fold.
This shape can determine the less severe
You can continue to take the effect of the 3D window while adjusting the breeches of the hat.
Move the neck part and the point downwards to increase the fabric of the folded part, which can make the fold of the collar deeper and the fold of the collar more obvious.
Use the inner line of the shoulder strap and the cut-and-cut sewing function to make a hemline.
Remove all the pins.
Then create the side of the skirt.
The side of the skirt is the front of the skirt.
The side of the skirt is the back of the skirt.
Harden all the side panels to make it easier to organize the shape quickly.
The side of the skirt is the front of the skirt.
After that, you can harden all the panels and adjust the pressure to 1 to quickly spread the skirt.
Add some pins in the right position to fix the skirt.
From the side, you will see that the skirt is not very smooth.
We first click to rotate the user-designed axis to the side of the two skirts, and then manually adjust the bottom to make the transition more natural.
Next, we will cut the princess line on the back piece.
As a reference, we can use the split function of the right-click menu bar to create a straight line point that will divide the shoulder line into two parts.
We also create a split point at the bottom of the skirt.
Then, based on these two points, we will draw the inner line.
Pay attention to create a point near the waist position to make it easier to adjust later.
Next, we will draw the cut line on the front piece and cut the seam allowance.
In the process of drawing the line, press the CTRL key to draw the curve point, and release the CTRL key to continue drawing the straight line point.
Double-click to complete the creation.
Move the waist point in the back to the side point to be in the same level line position.
Adjust the curve of the cut line.
Cut the seam allowance along this inner line.
Draw the cut line on the back piece to match the front piece.
Double-click to complete the creation of the inner line.
Then, select the right-click to increase the point to the outer line of the skirt.
Extend the cut line to the outer line of the skirt and create a cut point at the same time.
Then, use the
to select the cut line on the side and merge it in the menu in the right-click.
You can merge the cut line along the cut line.
Then adjust the bottom.
Delete excess points.
If you find some strange lines when moving the straight line point, you can press V to switch to the tool.
Then see if there is a line.
If there is, delete it.
Then continue to adjust the bottom.
After completion, convert the straight line point to the curve point.
Select the two lines.
In the menu bar on the right-click, select the inner line created by creating several equal lines.
Next, we will copy and paste the inner lines on these inner lines.
Isaiah
You can create plenty of lines by pressing Alt andön on the earlier and below lines.
Here, for instance, I will draw a line out, so do not use anテール.
Using the toolbar of the inner multif Bana to create a flower line on the back side.
Create an etaline line on the back.
Sit still here to draw define outlined lines.
Select the opening line in the front and then select the cut and sew in the right-click menu.
Expand the front and middle lines with the outside of the board.
Remember to select the inner line.
The newly created part is the front and middle lines of the following clothing.
Combine the lines together.
Next, we are going to create a button.
Use the button tool to create a button along the inner line.
Use the move button tool to copy and paste the button.
When pasting, press the right button.
You can open and paste the dialogue window.
You can manually enter the number of buttons copied.
Then switch to the button type window.
Select a type of button and change its shape in the attribute editor window below.
You can change the color of the button.
Select all the buttons and then select the button in the right-click menu to copy and paste the button to the symmetrical board.
Then select the button tool.
After selecting all the buttons, click on the button and remember them.
Remember them.
Then go to the Fabric folder in the library window.
There are a lot of fur fabrics in the library window.
They all start with fur.
Click and drag the fur and girl fabric to the blank area of the fabric type window.
Increase it to a fabric type.
Similarly, drag the wool-melted fabric to the blank area of the fabric type window.
Select all the panels and apply wool-melted fabric.
This is a thick wool fabric.
Then select all the side panels and apply fur-angora fabric.
Copy wool-melted fabric.
The name of the double-sided fabric can be changed.
Then select all the panels.
Then unzip all the panels.
Then we need to change the color of the fabric.
Before that, we need to click on the fill color under the texture option to color the material.
Then manually select a color you like.
In this way, the dark and light can be changed.
Next, select the fur-melted fabric and drag the fur into the color box.
Then change the color to light brown and color the fur in the same way.
Then select the color you like.
Then drag the fur into the color box.
Select the inside of the colon layer, and create a colon layer on the inside.
Then select the newly created version, select the release link, and then select the surface in the 3D window to turn them over, so that these two versions are also facing the outside when they are on the inside.
On the far left of the interface, you can change to the shop label. You can buy a lot of free items, including the posture and the name of the file we want to use.
You can click on the top sorting label and the item conditions at the bottom to check the specific category of the item.
Click on the plus icon to add the item to the shopping cart.
Here you can follow the operation in the video to buy some obvious products and virtual model posture.
After the purchase is completed, download these purchased files.
Download and download the posture file.
As the posture changes, the costume will also automatically simulate the appropriate position.
You can also change it to the background.
Switch to the
Next, use the line tool to add the line effect on the line.
Then adjust the color of the line or other attributes according to your needs.
Since the name line is created, the current type of name line is used.
Therefore, if you want to create another style of name line along the selected lines, remember to switch to other name line types in time before creating.
After creating the name line details, you can move on to the rendering of other common 3D software.
Let's take a look at the effect.
Here the effect looks like this in another city.
The effect is amazing.
This
this
this is such anнетic.?!"